

# **Profile**

With more than 8 years of IT expereince including a Bachelors Degree major in Web Design/Development. I am a well rounded skillset personality that has experience using HTML,CSS,Javascript along with using backend PHP language as well. My current position as a Enterprise Web Developer we do a combination of CMS management and PHP applications to keep the campus websites responsive and maintain PHP to collect data to a databse.

## **Contact**

Phone: 501-247-6443

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/michael-gray-dev

Website: www.michaeldgray.com

Email: mgray2@ualr.edu

### Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

PHP

Wordpress

Linux

Windows

Troubleshooting

### **Education**

**University of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

8/2020 - 5/2024

**Bachelor of Arts** 

Web Design & Development

**Pulaski Technical College** 

8/2013 - 12/2015

**Associates Degree** 

Comp Info Systems: Networking

## Experience

**Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

Enterprise Web Developer 04/2022 – Present

**Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock** 

Systems Administrator 06/2019 – 04/2022

**Windstream Communications** 

Network Analyst 04/2019 – 06/2019

SCA Pharmaceutical

Network Administrator 04/2019 – 06/2019

#### **AFMC**

IT support Specialist 06/2016 – 02/2019

**Dept of Human Services** 

Unified Comunication Specialist

06/2015 - 06/2016

**Windstream Communications** 

Network Analyst II 12/2012 – 04/2015